Matt: In terms of sound, not especially,
but that is because there were things that
I trained myself to, to find enjoyable.
So for instance, at home we had an
open fire and using a metal shovel
to scrape the ashes out of the grate
was a really difficult sound for me.
But I've I made myself get used to
that and actually working with sound
over the last decade has also helped
because I'm listening much more for
interesting nuances and how many
elements there are to particular sounds.
Physically, basically my feet are
incredibly sensitive, it's not a
problem when I'm walking, it is actually
very nice though if I'm at home and
I take my shoes and socks off...
do like very sort of soft,
smooth fabrics under my feet.
That's a really very
pleasurable sensation.
But beyond that, nothing much.